<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">asanecon</string>
    <string name="no_stocks">No Stocks</string>
    <string name="stock_add_hint">Input stock symbol here</string>
    <string name="portfolio_add_hint">Input portfolio name here</string>
    <string name="stock_add_button">Add</string>
    <string name="pe_target">PE Target</string>
    <string name="stop_loss">Stop Loss</string>
    <string name="cost_basis">Cost Basis</string>
    <string name="target_price">Target Price</string>
    <string name="pe_notifications">PE Notifications</string>
    <string name="target">Target</string>
    <string name="showCostBasis">Show Cost Basis</string>
    <string name="showCurrentPrice">Show Current Price</string>
    <string name="blank">""</string>
    <string name="accumulation_heavy">The stock is experiencing heavy trading volume on an up day. Indicates its being purchased by the big money managers.</string>
    <string name="accumulation_light">The stock is experiencing light trading volume on a down day. Indicates its being purchased by the big money managers.</string>
    <string name="distribution_heavy">The stock is experiencing heavy trading volume on a down day. Indicates its being sold by the big money managers.</string>
    <string name="distribution_light">The stock is experiencing light trading volume on an up day. Indicates its being sold by the big money managers.</string>
    <string name="breakout">The stock has hit its highest closing price in the last 60 days. Indicates a possible positive trend change.</string>
    <string name="downside">The stock has hit its lowest price in the last 90 days. Indicates a possible negative trend change.</string>
    <string name="bull_trend">The stock is trading above its 200 day moving average. Signals a possible bull trend.</string>
    <string name="bear_trend">The stock is trading below its 200 day moving average. Signals a possible bear trend.</string>
    <string name="up_trend">The stocks closing price has increased for 10 straight days. Indicates a possible positive breakout.</string>
    <string name="high_valuation">A PEG value greater than 2 signals a high valuation.</string>
    <string name="trailing_stop_loss">The stop loss defines the maximum percentage loss that is acceptable before a stock should be sold. A trailing stop loss protects gains by triggering when a stock closes the specified percentage below its highest price.</string>
    <string name="down_price_action">The stock is trading below its 50 day moving average indicating a momentum shift towards a bear trend.</string>
    <string name="undervalued"><![CDATA[
        The stock might be undervalued.
        <ul>
            <li>The enterprise value multiple (EV/EBITDA) indicates how long it would take an acquisition to earn enough to pay off its costs. A multiple of 10 or lower might indicate the stock is undervalued.</li>
            <li>A Price/Earnings to Growth (PEG) ratio &lt; 1 indicates the stock might be undervalued.</li>
            <li>A stock price lower than the book value per share might indicate the stock has been undervalued by the market.</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="profitability"><![CDATA[
        The company profitability/liquidity should be further analyzed.
        <ul>
            <li>A current ratio &lt 1 means the company might not meet its debt obligations. Not always the case though.</li>
            <li>Its preferable for the operating margin to be &gt 15%.</li>
            <li>A lower debt to equity ratio value means the company is less leveraged (has less debt).</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="management_effectiveness" formatted="false"><![CDATA[
        Management performance should be further analyzed.
        <ul>
            <li>The return on assets indicates how profitable a company is relative to assets and should be no less than 5%.</li>
            <li>The return on equity indicates how effectively shareholder money is being used by management. A value between 15 to 20% is considered good.</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="volatility">The stock is %1$s%% less volatile than the overall stock market.</string>

</resources>
