<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">asanecon</string>
    <string name="no_stocks">No Stocks</string>
    <string name="stock_add_hint">Input stock symbol here</string>
    <string name="portfolio_add_hint">Input portfolio name here</string>
    <string name="stock_add_button">Add</string>
    <string name="pe_target">PE Target</string>
    <string name="stop_loss">Stop Loss</string>
    <string name="buy_price">Buy Price</string>
    <string name="target_price">Target Price</string>
    <string name="pe_notifications">PE Notifications</string>
    <string name="target">Target</string>
    <string name="showCostBasis">Show Cost Basis</string>
    <string name="showCurrentPrice">Show Current Price</string>
    <string name="blank">""</string>
    <string name="accumulation_heavy">The stock is experiencing heavy trading volume on an up day. Indicates its being purchased by the big money managers.</string>
    <string name="accumulation_light">The stock is experiencing light trading volume on a down day. Indicates its being purchased by the big money managers.</string>
    <string name="distribution_heavy">The stock is experiencing heavy trading volume on a down day. Indicates its being sold by the big money managers.</string>
    <string name="distribution_light">The stock is experiencing light trading volume on an up day. Indicates its being sold by the big money managers.</string>
    <string name="breakout">The stock has hit its highest closing price in the last 60 days. Indicates a possible positive trend change.</string>
    <string name="downside">The stock has hit its lowest price in the last 90 days. Indicates a possible negative trend change.</string>
    <string name="bull_trend">The stock is trading above its 200 day moving average. Signals a possible bull trend.</string>
    <string name="bear_trend">The stock is trading below its 200 day moving average. Signals a possible bear trend.</string>
    <string name="up_trend">The stocks closing price has increased for 10 straight days. Indicates a possible positive breakout.</string>
    <string name="high_valuation">A PEG value greater than 2 signals a high valuation.</string>
    <string name="trailing_stop_loss">The stop loss defines the maximum percentage loss that is acceptable before a stock should be sold. A trailing stop loss protects gains by triggering when a stock closes the specified percentage below its highest price.</string>
    <string name="down_price_action">The stock is trading below its 50 day moving average indicating a momentum shift towards a bear trend.</string>
</resources>
